Resiliency doesn't stop with a region or VPC.
弹性不会随区域或 VPC停止
Creating a platform that is holistically available
创建整体可用的平台
requires resiliency throughout each part of your service.
在服务的每个部分都需要弹性
To have a resilient platform,
要有一个弹性平台
all parts of it need to be fault tolerant.
它的所有部分都需要容错
As you decide if a service needs to tolerate failures,
当您决定服务是否需要容忍失败时
you can let that decision drive choices about whether to
您可以让该决策选择是否
spend the time and dollars to make your applications resilient.
花费时间和美元使您的应用程序具有弹性
Should you desire to,
如果你愿意
AWS provides you the tools you need to make all components resilient.
AWS 为您提供了使所有组件具有弹性所需的工具
In this lesson, you'll practice driving redundancy
在本课程中 您将练习驱动冗余
throughout your system by ensuring that not only the underlying network,
在整个系统中 确保不仅是底层网络
but also the individual services on top of it are highly available.
但也有高度的个人服务